Guide to the Administrative Papers of the Chancellor Harry Woodburn Chase 1933-1951 RG.3.0.5
New York University Archives
- Series I: World War II
  - Selective Service
    - University of the State of New York Rehabilitation Plans, undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - State Board of Regents Technical Institute Plans, 1943-1948 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - State Board of Regents Academic Credit Discussions, 1942-1944 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Congressional Bills concerning the Vets, Rehabilitation and Education, 1943-1946 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Criticism, and Discussion of Bills, undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Veterans' Guidance Center, 1945-1946 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Veterans' Manual, 1945 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - General Materials Including Digest on Veterans, 1944 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Veterans' Education at University-Government Contracts, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Veteran's Counselling Service, 1944-1946 (Box 18, Folder 5 - 7)
    - School of Commerce, Dr. Gregory Mason, undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Division of General Education, Professor Paul A. McGhee, undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - School of Education, Professor Roland H. Spaulding, undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - College of Engineering, Professor Mario C. Giannini, undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Graduate Division for Training in Public Service, Professor Emanual Stein, undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Graduate School of Business Administration, Dr. Coleman L. Maze, undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Graduate School of Arts and Science, Professor Lois McDonald, undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - School of Law, Dean Arthur Vanderbilt, undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Libraries, Dean Joseph H. Park, undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - University College, Professor John W. McConnell, undated (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Washington Square College, Professor Casper J. Kraemer, undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Washington Square College, Physics, Professor C. W. van der Merwe, undated (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - University Committee on Rehabilitation and Education, undated (Box 18, Folder 20 - 21)
    - Veterans' Collegiate Association, undated (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Veterans' Housing Project, undated (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Universal Military Training, 1944-1948 (Box 18, Folder 24 - 25)
    - Voorhis Memo, October, 1944 and Replies concerning the Scholarships for Veterans, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Inquiries, Statements, Suggestions about the Rehabilitation and Post War Educational Plans, 1943-1945 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Suggestions from Outside Sources and Plans of Other organizations, 1944-1945 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - The State Veterans' Commission, 1944 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence about Post-War Plans, 1943-1945 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Pamphlets, Congressional Bill, Publications, Press Releases, etc., undated (Box 19, Folder 6 - 7)
    - Miscellaneous Letters to Alumni and Families Concerning the Wounded and Prisoners, 1943-1946 (Box 19, Folder 8 - 9)
    - Letters of Condolence, Gold Star Provisions, 1942-1947 (Box 20, Folder 1 - 4)
    - Letters of Congratulations to the Promoted and Decorated, 1943-1946 (Box 20, Folder 5 - 10)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence to and from Alumni; Alumni Bulletin, undated (Box 21, Folder 1 - 3)
    - Christmas Cards Sent to Former Students and Replies, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Lists of Promotions, Casualties, Citations, etc., from Alumni Office, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Letter to Returning Servicemen of September, 1945 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Selective Service Memos, ROTC Memo, undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Copies of Letters and Memos to Deans, Faculty, and Students, undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Copies of Letters and Memos to Deans, Faculty, and Students, undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Copies of Letters and Memos to Alumni, Parents, Deans, etc., undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Copies of Letters and Memos to Deans, Faculty, and Administration, undated (Box 21, Folder 11 - 13)
    - Copies of Specimen Letters to Former Students and Graduates, undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Material on National Defense Programs and Higher Education, undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Letters, Memos, Press Releases, ASTP, Navy, A.C.E., etc. Printed, undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Form Letters To Deans, Students, undated (Box 22, Folder 4 - 5)
    - Form Letters and Memos about University Policies, undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - ASTP Instruction Letter, Feb 2, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Publications, Various, Received by N.Y.U., undated (Box 22, Folder 8 - 9)
    - Publications, Various, Received by N.Y.U., (continued), undated (Box 23, Folder 1 - 4)
    - Miscellaneous Printed Matter: ASTP, Navy, A.C.E., etc., undated (Box 23, Folder 5 - 6)
    - A.C.E. Bulletins, 1940-1943 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - A.C.E. Bulletins, Duplicate Copies, May 1940, July 1945 (Box 24, Folder 2 - 4)
    - A.C.E. Bulletins and Minutes of Meeting, April 1943 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - A.C.E. Bulletins, 1945-1949 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - A.C.E. Bulletins with Emergency Supplements, 1945-1950 (Box 25, Folder 1 - 2)
  - Subseries: Miscellaneous War - Related Correspondence
    - Goodwill Gesture to Japan, 1936 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Public Survey Re: Peace or War, 1941 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Series II: Administrative Correspondence
  - Citizens Committee for a Second Front, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - All-University Alumni Dinner, Nov 1946 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - American Student Union, 1937-1940 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Annual Reports: Correspondence, 1934-1950 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Architecture and Allied Arts, 1935 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Architecture and Allied Arts, 1936 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Architecture and Allied Arts, 1936-1937 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Architecture and Allied Arts, 1937-1938 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Architecture and Allied Arts, 1938-1939 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Architecture and Allied Arts, 1939-1940 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Architecture and Allied Arts, 1940-1941 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Architecture and Allied Arts: Discontinuance of Work at 1071 6th Avenue, Bryant Park Center, 1940-1941 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Architecture and Allied Arts: Discontinuance of work at 1071 6th Avenue, Bryant Park Center, 1940-1941 (Box 26, Folder 1 - 2)
  - Architecture and Allied Arts: Report of Faculty Committee on Future Development, 1940 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Architecture and Allied Arts: Terminal Course, 1941-1946 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1933-1943 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Association of Life Insurance Presidents, 1933 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Athletic Situation, 1933-1934 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Athletic Situation, 1935 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Athletics: J.V. Gilloon (Director of Athletics), 1950-1951 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Axworthy, H. Harold (Director, Bureau of Community Service and Research), 1937-1941 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Babcock, Earl B. (Director of European Center of Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, Professor of Romance Language and Literature Administrative Officer), 1933-1936 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Badger, Phillip 0. (Chairman, University Board of Athletic Control; President, N.C.A.A.), 1933-1936 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Baer, William B. (Dean, University College of and Science), 1941-1950 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Balliet, Thomas (former Dean of School of Education); Library for Teachers donated by Professor Paul Radosavljevich in memory of Balliet, 1942-1946 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Barney Building: Center for Industrial Arts, 1939-1940 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Berg, Albert A. (Surgeon), Jun 1943 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Biblotheca Belgica: Belgian literature collection, 1935-1939 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Blumenthal, George (Trustee and Chairman of Executive and Finance Committee), 1934-1941 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Board of Athletic Control, 1943-1944 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Board of Athletic Control, 1944-1945 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Board of Athletic Control, 1945-1946 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Board of Athletic Control, 1946-1947 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Board of Athletic Control, 1947-1948 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Board of Athletic Control, 1948-1949 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Board of Control of All-University Non-Athletic Student Activities, 1934-1941 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Board of Control of All-University Non-Athletic Student Activities, 1945-1948 (Box 28, Folder 1 - 2)
  - Board of Student Health, 1934-1937 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Booz, Allen, and Hamilton: Proposed Top Line Organization for, undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - New York University, 1950 (Box 28)
  - Bossange, Raymond (Dean, School of Architecture and Allied Arts), 1933-1941 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Bouton, Archibald L. (Dean, University College; Chairman, Department of English), 1933-1941 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Brisco, Morris A. (Dean, School of Retailing), 1943-1944 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Browder, Earl: Refused permission to speak at NYU, 1939-1941 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Elmer Ellsworth Brown House for English Study, 1935, 1938 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Brown, Chancellor E. E.: Portrait, 1939-1941' (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Brown, Marshall S. (Dean of Faculties), 1933-1940' (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Brown, Marshall S., 1934 (Box 28, Folder 12 - 13)
  - Brown, Marshall S., 1934 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Brown, Marshall S., 1934 (Box 28, Folder 15 - 16)
  - Brown, Marshall S., 1934 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Brown, Marshall S., 1934 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Budget Discussions, 1941-1942' (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Bureau of Employment, 1937-1942' (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Bureau of Employment, 1939 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Center for Human Relations Studies, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Chambers, Robert, 1938 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - A Unique Laboratory in the City - Laboratory of Cellular Physiology, undated (Box 29)
  - Chapel Exercises, University Heights, 1934-1943 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Charter Revision, New York City Charter, 1934-1937 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Chancellor Chase, Convocation for, Oct 2, 1933 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Chancellor Chase, Personal Correspondence, 1942-1950 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Chancellor Chase Portrait, Jun 1948 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Chancellor Chase's Residence, 1939-1947 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Chancellor Chase's Retirement, 1950-1951 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Chancellor Chase's Vacation, Jul 1934-Aug 1934 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Christian Association, 1933-1950 (Box 30, Folder 1 - 2)
  - Circular Letters, Miscellaneous, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Civil Aeronautics Authority, 1938, 1939 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Clem, Orlie M. (Instructor in Education), 1937-1943 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - College Teachers Union, 1941-1947 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Columbia Broadcasting System, 1937-1939 (Box 30, Folder 7 - 8)
  - Columbia Broadcasting System, 1938-1940 (Box 30, Folder 9 - 10)
  - Columbia Broadcasting System, 1938-1941 (Box 31, Folder 1 - 2)
  - Columbia Broadcasting System, 1941-1945 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Commencement, Jun 8, 1933 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Commencement: Installation of H. W. Chase as Chancellor, Jun 13, 1934 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Commencement: Installation of H. W. Chase as Chancellor, Jun 13, 1934 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Commencement: Installation of H. W. Chase as Chancellor, Jun 13, 1934 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Commencement: Installation of H.W. Chase as Chancellor, Jun 13, 1934 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Commencement, Jun 12, 1935 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Commencement, Jun 10, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, Jun 9, 1937 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Commencement, - First Doctor of Medicine, Jun 9, 1937 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Commencement, Jun 8, 1938 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Commencement, Jun 7, 1939 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Commencement, Jun 5, 1940 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Commencement, Jun 11, 1941 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Commencement, Jun 10, 1942 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Commencement and Special Graduations, 1943 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Commencement and Special Graduations, 1943 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Commencement and Special Graduations, 1943 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Luncheon, Jun 9, 1943 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Luncheon, Jun 9, 1943 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Luncheon, 1934-1942 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Commerce, Accounts, and Finance, School of, 1936-1938 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Commerce, Accounts, and Finance, School of, 1940-1942, 1944 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Commerce, Accounts, and Finance, School of, 1943-1946 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Commerce, Accounts, and Finance, School of, 1945-1947 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Commerce, Accounts, and Finance, School of, 1948-1950 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Commission on Financing Higher Education, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Allocation of Space at Washington Square, 1937-1946 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Examinations (Irregularities in Examinations), Apr 15, 1935 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Insurance and Annuities, 1939-1950 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Committee on the Liberal Arts Colleges, 1933-1934 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Machine Shop, 1941 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Management of Bookstore andUniversityPress, 1935 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - '1938-1941, 1945-1946 (Box 34)
  - Committee on Mathematics, 1942 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Tenure and Promotions, 1934-1937 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Tenure and Promotions, 1938-1939 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Tenure and Promotions, 1940-1947 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Committee on University Research in Relation to Federal Science Legislation, 1946-1947 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Committees, Circular Letters to, 1937-1943 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Comptroller and Assistant Treasurer (Leroy E. Kimball), 1941-1943 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Conference of Deans - Recommendation of Rufus D. Smith to the position of Provost, 1933-1934 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Council and Committees, Dec 22, 1941-1945, 1947-1948 (Box 35, Folder 6 - 7)
  - The Council of NYU, Circular Letters to, 1933-1951 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Council Committee, 1931-1932, 1934-1935 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Council Dinner, 1934 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Council Dinner, 1935 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Council Dinner -Telegram sent to female guest of honor, who was not allowed to attend because she was a woman, 1936 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Council Dinner - Edna St. Vincent Millay, an honorary degree candidate, was excluded from the dinner, 1937 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Council Dinner, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Council Dinner, 1939 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Council Dinner, 1940 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Council Dinner, 1941 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Counsel, University - John Gerdes, 1940-1943 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Courant, Professor Richard (Head of the Graduate Department of Mathematics, Director of Research for the Institute for Applied Mathematics and Mechanics), 1933-1938, 1942-1943 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Cox, Richard T. (Professor of Physics), 1934-1935 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Craven, Wesley Frank (Professor of History), 1946, 1949 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Deans and Faculty, Circular Letters to, 1933-1950 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Deans at Washington Square, 1945 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Deans' Meetings, 1945-1946 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Dearborn, Ned H. (Professor of Education, Dean of the Division of General Education), 1934-1943 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Deans' Lectures, 1933-1949 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Delafield Papers - Correspondence regarding transfer of, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Dentistry, College of, 1936-1950 (Box 36, Folder 11 - 12)
  - Dentistry, College of - Administration and Reorganization, 1936-1937, 1940-1942 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Dentistry, College of -AdministrationandReorganization, 1942-1945 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Dentistry, College of: Administration and Reorganization, 1943-1944 (Box 37, Folder 1 - 2)
  - Dentistry, College of: Administration and Reorganization, 1944-1946 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Dentistry, College of: Administration and Reorganization, 1945-1946 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Dentistry, College of: Administration and Reorganization, 1943-1945 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Eagleton, Clyde (Professor of International Law), 1932 (Box 37, Folder 6 - 7)
  - Eagleton, Clyde (Professor of International Law), 1933-1936, 1939-1949 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Education, Conference on, Nov 2, 1933-Nov 3, 1933 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Education, Office of, U.S. Department of Interior, 1933-1937 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Education, Secondary, 1933 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Education, School of, 1926, 1936-1949 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Education, School of, 1940 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Education, School of, 1940-1941 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Education, School of, 1942-1945 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Education, School of, 1946-1948 (Box 38, Folder 4 - 5)
  - Education, School of, 1948-1950 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Education, School of, 1949-1950 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Education, School of, 1948-1949 (Box 38, Folder 8 - 9)
  - Education, School of - Deanship, Ernest Oscar Melby, 1944-1945 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Education, School of, 1944-1945 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Education, School of, 1944-1945 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Educational Film Institute, 1938-1939 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Educational Film Institute, 1939-1940 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Educational Film Institute: Film Library, 1940-1942 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Educational Film Institute: Film Library, 1941-1942 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Educational Film Institute: Film Library, 1941-1942 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Educational Film Institute - Motion Pictures Department,FilmLibrary, 1943-1946 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Emergency Work Bureau Activities, 1929-1933 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Employment, Bureau of, 1943-1944 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Engineering, College of, 1932-1938 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Engineering, College of, 1938-1942 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Engineering, College of, 1937-1945 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Engineering, College of - Institute of Aeronautical Sciences, 1942 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Enrollment and Registration, 1934 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Faculty: Outside Activities, 1938-1940 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Faculty: Outside Activities, 1940-1942 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Club, 1938-1939 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Club, 1940-1950 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Club, 1940-1941 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Fees, Student, 1935-1937 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Fees, Student, 1937 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Finance Committee, 1935-1948 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Finance Committee, 1949-1950 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Finance Committee - Radio Broadcasts, 1939 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Financial Reports (Confidential) by Dean Rufus D. Smith, 1933 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Financial Situation - NYU, 1943-1944 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Financial Situation - NYU, 1943-1944 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Financial Situation - NYU, 1943-1944 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Financial Situation - NYU, 1943-1944 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Fine Arts, College of/Graduate Center of, 1933-1937 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Fine Arts, Institute of, 1938-1941 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Fine Arts, Institute of, 1942-1943 (Box 42, Folder 1 - 2)
  - Fine Arts, Institute of, 1944-1946 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Fine Arts, Institute of, 1947-1950 (Box 42, Folder 4 - 5)
  - Finley, Dr. John H. (Director, Hall of Fame), 1937-1940 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - First American Youth Congress, 1934 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Folks, Ralph (NYU Attorney), 1933-1940 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Food Law Institute, 1949-1950 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Foreign Student Center, 1949-1951 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Franklin and Marshall College, 1937 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Fraternity Council of NYU, 1933-1935 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Friedsam Estate, 1934-1939 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Fryer, Professor Douglas H. (Psychology Department), 1934-1935 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Gaisman, Henry J. (Inventors' Foundation), 1938, 1940-1941 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - General Education Board., 1934-1937 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Folder Dates, undated (Box 43)
  - General Education, Division of, 1933-1934 (Box 43, Folder 7 - 8)
  - General Education, Division of, 1934-1936 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - General Education, Division of, 1936-1937 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - General Education, Division of, Jan 1938Jul 1938 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - General Education, Division of, 1938-1939 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - General Education, Division of, 1940 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - General Education, Division of, 1941 (Box 44, Folder 2 - 3)
  - General Education, Division of, 1942-1950 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Gifts, Chancellor's Committee to Review, 1943-1944 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Goldman Band Concerts, 1936 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Graduate Division for Training in Public Service, 1936-1937 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Graduate Division for Training in Public Service, 1937-1938 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Graduate Division for Training in Public Service, 1938-1939 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Graduate Division for Training in Public Service, 1940 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Graduate Division for Training in Public Service, 1941-1942, 1944-1945 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Graduate Division for Training in Public Service, 1946-1948 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Graduate Division of Public Service, 1949-1951 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1934 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1939-1942, 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - 1948, 1950, undated (Box 45)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration, 1936-1937, 1939 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - 1942-1950, undated (Box 45)
  - Graduate Work, University Commission on, 1937-1943 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Gueft, Dr. Amshel (Professor of Dentistry), 1935-1937 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Guggenheim School of Aeronautics, 1941-1942, 1945 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Hall of Fame, 1932-1936 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Hall of Fame, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Hall of Fame, 1938-1939 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Hall of Fame, 1940 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Hall of Fame, 1941-1943 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Hall of Fame, 1944-1950 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Halley, Robert B. - Gift of, 1942-1943 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Harvard Tercentenary, 1935-1936 (Box 46, Folder 5 - 6)
  - Hebrew Technical Institute Building, 1938-1939 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Heidelberg University's 550th Anniversary Celebration, 1936 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Hering, Professor Daniel W. (Physics Department), 1933-1938 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Hesser, Ernest G. (Chairman, Department of Music), 1939 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Hirshland, Dr. George S. (Department of Government), 1939-1940 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Hofstra College (Nassau College - Hofstra Memorial), 1935 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Hofstra College (Nassau College - Hofstra Memorial), 1935 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Hofstra College (Nassau College - Hofstra Memorial), 1936 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Hofstra College (of New York University), 1937 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Hofstra College (of New York University), 1937 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Hofstra College (of New York University), 1938 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Hofstra College (of New York University), 1939 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Hofstra College (of New York University), 1939 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Hofstra College (of New York University), 1939 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Hofstra College, 1939 (Box 47, Folder 7 - 8)
  - Hofstra College, 1939 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Horne, Professor Herman H. (Chairman of the Departments of Philosophy and Historyof Education), 1933-1938 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Horne, Professor Herman H., 1938-1943 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Institute of Arts & Sciences, 1933-1934 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Institute of Applied Mathematics/Institute for MathematicsandMechanics-RichardCourant, 1940-1946 (Box 47, Folder 13 - 14)
  - Institute of Applied Mathematics/Institute for Mathematics and Mechanics - Richard Courant, 1947-1950 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Institute of Economic Affairs, 1946-1950 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Institute of International Education - Harrison Brown and W. Arnold Forster, 1936-1938 (Box 48, Folder 3)